

Tegar Subkhan Fauzi, S.Kom. Web Developer

Purwokerto, Indonesia 🔒 +62 89666288087 Purwokerto, 11 October 1998 tegarsubkhan236@gmail.com

tegarsubkhanfauzi.netlify.app





# **OBJECTIVE**

Experienced Website Developer with +1 year of professional experience in consulting company for manage the various phases of developing operations. Able to handle multiple and challenging projects with minimum supervision. Motivated to offer the highest quality service with full focus on flow, productivity and efficiency issues.

Birthday : 11 October 1998 : +62 89 666 288 087 Phone

: Purwokerto, Central Java, Indonesia City

: 23 Aae

Degree : Bachelor



### **EDUCATION**

# Information System | UNIKOM, Bandung

AUG 2016 - AUG 2021

Undergraduate degree – GPA: 3.51 / 4.00 (149 / 160 credits)

Research: Development of Distributed Academic Information System of Institut Kesehatan Rajawali, Bandung, West Java



# **EXPERIENCE**





APR 2021 - JUNE 2021

- Build student report system.at Siswamedia
- Design and implement landing page at Siswamedia
- Build extracurricular system.at Siswamedia

### S5 IT Consultant | Junior Web Developer



APR 2018 - FEB 2020

- Contributed to build PMB system at Institut Kesehatan Rajawali.
- Contributed to build SIAKAD system at Intitut Kesehatan Rajawali
- Contributed to build Cipta Pasar as QA.
- Complete various UNIKOM student thesis project



HARD SKILLS

■ SCRUM

■ HTML / CSS / Bootstrap ■ Teamwork

GIT

Laravel

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

Adaptability

Analytical Thinking and Creative



## **ACTIVITIES AND CERTIFICATIONS**

- Committee in the "Sunat Masal" event in Garut, 2019
- Committee in the "Nikah Masal" event in Garut, 2019
- · Certificate of competence Programming and Software Development (Junior Web Programmer), 2019